- Hello, I'm Ncuti, and I play Eric.
- Hi, I'm Emma, and I play Maeve.
- And I'm Asa.
I play Otis.
And we are about to take a quiz
to find out which Sex
Education character we are.
(upbeat music)
- First, how would your BFFs describe you?
- [Emma] Smart, creative,
funny, impulsive, bold, honest.
What'd you say?
- You I would describe
as funny, smart, and one of them.
- Funny, smart, creative,
okay, all of them, yeah.
- Shoot, I would say, but
you're a bit of everything.
- Bold.
- You're bold.
- Because bold means everything.
- You're funny.
- It's a Libra thing.
- I think you gotta be
hissing the air, bold.
You're bold.
- Bold.
Okay, bold.
(laughing)
- Bold.
You're...
- I don't know.
- I would say you're impulsive.
- Am I creative or impulsive?
Am I impulsive?
- Are you impulsive?
- I feel like you are.
- Sometimes.
- You're an Aries.
- But you're also very smart.
Ah, this is very hard.
This is question one, and we're like,
- I know.
- "Which option am I really?"
How would you describe me?
- I know.
Who am I?
- Honest?
- Emma, say, "Smart."
- Are you honest?
- I could be more honest.
- Are you lying to me?
Fine.
Choose a class to attend.
How to take a great #Selfie.
(laughing)
The art of cooking.
The science of Harry Potter.
Feminist literature 101.
Lego robotics.
(laughing)
And sex education.
- I'm gonna say...
- Lego robotics.
- The art of cooking.
- Oh, okay fine.
- Oh, why?
- No, that's fine.
- He already knows how
to take a great selfie.
- I don't need to go to class for that.
- He is the teacher.
- I'm the professor.
I might do the science of
Harry Potter, you know.
- That's what I!
(laughing)
I'm between those two.
No, I'm good.
I'm just gonna do science of Harry Potter.
- Okay, fun.
- 'cause I can cook quite well.
Not to brag.
- Lego robotics.
Pick a place at school to
make-out with your crush.
- Ooh, I like this one!
- The bathroom.
- [Emma] The library.
- [Asa] The empty classroom.
- [Emma] Sorry.
- [Asa] The cafeteria.
Or the locker room.
- The library.
- Oh, it's gotta be locker room.
Are you mad?
- But like it's a corridor, though,
it's quite daunting.
- [Asa] Library is
quite sort of secretive.
- [Emma] The playgrounds quite sweet,
but the library's is hot.
Everyone loves a little
cheeky library snogging.
(laughing)
it's very unhygienic.
- But they clean every day.
- Wait, all they said was make out.
- It's not sex.
Jesus.
- I'm gonna do empty classroom.
- Pick something to eat
at the school's cafeteria.
- [Asa] Pizza, salad,
peanut butter sandwich,
chicken nuggets, fruit
salad, or a milkshake.
- I wouldn't trust anything
in a school cafeteria.
- I'm gonna do fruit salad.
- I was gonna do... yeah fine.
We can both do the same.
- We can both do fruit salad.
- Milkshake or pizza.
(laughing)
- Milkshake.
- It's gonna be pizza because
you don't eat a milkshake.
And you wanna have some
food you wanna have like
- We don't like dairy.
We don't eat dairy.
- Exactly, we don't.
- Which character would
you trust with a secret?
- [Ncuti] Jackson, Lily,
Ola, Viv, Rahim, or Issac.
- Well, Jackson.
- Might be Lily.
- I'm gonna say...
- I'm gonna say Jackson.
- I'm gonna say Rahim.
- Did we all go for someone
that's not our character?
- Choose something important
from sex education.
Otis's sex clinic, Maeve's
essay prize trophy,
the Quiz Heads, Hedwig and the
Angry Inch, Lily's musical,
Moordale Secondary School.
That's a very tricky.
- What do you mean?
What does it mean choose
something important?
- They're all important.
- They're all.
I'm gonna say Otis's sex clinic.
- Instinctively I'm saying Quiz Heads,
because the font's bigger,
and I love the Quiz Heads.
- See, but I feel like a
lot of these things wouldn't
happen without Moordale.
- That's very true.
- Yeah that's true.
- See, he's wise as well.
- Wise, that should have been an option.
- That's what I was gonna say.
- So what, you mean as in
Moordale Secondary School?
- I've picked.
I pick Moordale.
- And I love them, I do love them as well,
and I'm gonna pick Quiz Heads.
- I'm gonna pick Otis's sex clinic,
just because I think you
have such wise words.
Finally, pick something
to binge watch on Netflix.
- [Ncuti] Schitt's Creek,
The End of the F**ing World,
Atypical, Chilling Adventures of Sabrina,
Strangest...
- Strangest Things.
- Stranger Things.
(laughing)
- Grace and Frankie.
- Do you know what?
I haven't watched the second season
of End of the F**ing World.
- No, I haven't seen the second season.
- I have watched...
- I haven't seen a few of these.
- We all binged Stranger Things.
- I've never seen...
- You haven't seen it.
- That's fine, that's fine.
- I haven't watched
the most recent season.
- I'm gonna say Sabrina
because I like witchy stuff.
(Gasps)
- I didn't say that.
- Sorry.
- Um, I'm gonna pick Stranger
Things because I just
need to get...
(yelling)
- Oh my God.
(laughing)
- That makes me so,
they make me these...
Okay.
- What the hell?
- Which character did you get?
- I got Eric Effiong.
Your personality matches
Eric, you're outgoing,
sincere, and passionate,
like Eric you march to
the beat of your own drum.
You don't care what other people think.
Your friends often turn to you
if they want to have a good time.
- Aw!
It's true.
- It's so true.
- I got Aimee Gibbs.
Your personality matches Aimee.
You're charismatic, bold, and fierce.
Like Aimee, you're extremely confident,
while some people might
consider you popular,
you'd much rather have a
quiet night in with your BFFs
than hang at a party.
You'll do anything to help your friends.
- Yes!
That's very true.
- Wow.
This is incredibly accurate, so far.
I got Adam Groff.
- Two coke cans.
(laughing)
- Your personality matches Adam.
You're impulsive,
assertive, and enthusiastic.
Like Adam, you're still
trying to find out your place
in this world, whilst you're
often seen as intimidating,
deep down you're incredibly sweet.
- The least intimidating person.
- What do you mean?
(laughing)
- Aw, I enjoyed that.
I'm so glad I got Aimee.
- Yeah.
- That's lovely.
And I would rather have a
quiet night in, actually.
- Yeah.
- And I'll do anything
for you two, I will.
- Well, hope you enjoyed
that quiz, we sure did.
(laughing)
If you wanna take it, check out Buzzfeed,
it's on there, and watch
Sex Education season two,
it's on Netflix now.
- Yeah!
Watch it!
- Watch it.
- [All] Bye!
(upbeat music)